let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "___________ is an easy way to collect information from a user?",
    answer: "HTML Form",
    options: [
      "HTML Form",
      "HTML Hyperlinks",
      "HTML Images",
      "HTML Lists"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "For a single line of input ___________ feild is used.",
    answer: "Textarea",
    options: [
      "Check Box",
      "Text Box",
      "Textarea",
      "Radio Button"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following should be used while sending passwords or other sensitive information?",
    answer: "Post",
    options: [
      "Post",
      "First",
      "Get",
      "Target"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "__________ lets user select one or more options.?",
    answer: "Check Box",
    options: [
      "Radio Button",
      "Check Box",
      "Submit Button",
      "Text Area"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "____________ allows users to select only one of the given options.",
    answer: "Radio Button",
    options: [
      "Check Box",
      "Radio Button",
      "Text Area",
      "Submit"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Wat does <b> CSS </b> stands for?",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheets",
    options: [
      "Cascading Style Sheets",
      "Cascading Sheets Style",
      "Cascading HTML Style",
      "Cascading Style Shorts"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the below is not a style of CSS writing?",
    answer: "Extention",
    options: [
      "Inline",
      "Internal",
      "External",
      "Extention"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the below is the correct CSS declaration?",
    answer: "h1 {color: red;}",
    options: [
      "h1 {color- red;}",
      "h2 {color = red;}",
      "h1 {color: red;}",
      "h2 {red:color;"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which tag is used to connect external CSS files?",
    answer: "<link>>",
    options: [
      "<connect>",
      "<link>>",
      "<style>",
      "<href>"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following tags is used to write internal CSS code? ",
    answer: "<style>",
    options: [
      "<inline>",
      "<internal>",
      "<style>",
      "<link>"
    ]
  },



];